Othniel Charles Marsh Archives
Yale Peabody Museum of Natural History
- Correspondence, 1854-1899; Series II
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866-1898, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1531., 001877
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1882; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1535., 001881
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1540., 001886
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=196-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1541., 001887
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1542., 001888
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870-1875; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1544., 001890
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870-1871; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1546., 001892
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1870; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1555., 001901
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1556., 001902
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1882; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1558., 001904
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1879-1891; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1570., 001916
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1873; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1574., 001920
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1878; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1576., 001922
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1879-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1580., 001926
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1894-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1581., 001927
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1884-1890, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1582., 001928
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1881-188?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1583., 001929
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1885-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1584., 001930
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1585., 001931
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1885-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1588., 001934
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1875-1885; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1589., 001935
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1590., 001936
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1879-1881; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1591., 001937
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1892-1894; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1593., 001939
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866-1888; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1594., 001940
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1890-1891; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1596., 001942
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1895-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1603., 001949
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1876; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1606., 001952
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1892; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1607., 001953
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1612., 001958
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1883; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1615., 001961
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1878; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1617., 001963
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1619., 001965
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1887-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1623., 001969
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1899, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1624., 001970
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1892; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1625., 001971
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1626., 001972
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1878-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1628., 001974
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1875; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1630., 001976
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1881-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1631., 001977
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1889-189?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1633., 001979
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1895-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1634., 001980
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1898, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1635., 001981
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1897-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1636., 001982
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1894-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1637., 001983
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1870-1871; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1639., 001985
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1890-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1642., 001988
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1896-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1645., 001991
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1873-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1648., 001994
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1893-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1654., 002000
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1875-1877; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1658., 002004
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1897-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1659., 002005
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1880-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1660., 002006
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877, n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1661., 002007
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1662., 002008
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1876-18?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1666., 002012
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1876; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1667., 002013
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1869-1894; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1670., 002016
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1671., 002017
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1868-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1674., 002020
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1880-188?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1682., 002028
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1896-1898; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1683., 002029
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1875-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1684., 002030
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1877-1893; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1694., 002040
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1878-1880; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1696., 002042
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1876-1885; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1697., 002043
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1889-1890; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1699., 002045
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1889-1890; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1700., 002046
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=n d; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1701., 002047
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866-1869; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1702., 002048
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866-1874; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1704., 002050
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1881-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1705., 002051
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1876-187?; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1707., 002053
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1866-1887; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1708., 002054
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1892-1895; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1710., 002056
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1892-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1711., 002057
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1892-1897; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1715., 002061
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1875-1899; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1717., 002063
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1877; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1722., 002068
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1879-1881; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1723., 002069
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1871-1877; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1725., 002071
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1862-1873; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1730., 002076
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1874-1875; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1731., 002077
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1872-1889; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1732., 002078
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1882-1894; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1735., 002081
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original at Manuscripts and Archives, Sterling Memorial Library; unadjusted date string=1880-1896; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1737., 002083
  - Letter(s) to O. C. Marsh. Original letters from Morrison, Colorado sent between September 25, 1877 and February (or March), 1878. The letters include some small sketches including at least two of reconstructions of animals. Also, a set of photocopies of the letters.; unadjusted date string=1877-1878; ex Argus ID=VP.DOC.1782., 002126
  - Red Cloud. Correspondence from Red Cloud to O.C. Marsh., 002557
- Memorabilia, Series III
  O.C. Marsh memorabilia
  - Memorabilia., 002744
- Manuscript Materials, Series IV
  O.C. Marsh manuscript materials.
  - Manuscript Materials., 002763
- Research Materials, Series V
  O.C. Marsh research materials. Notes, sketches, etc.
  - Drawings, Sketches, etc., 000291
  - Locality Information., 000290
  - Research Notes., 000292
- Miscellaneous, Series VI
  O. C. Marsh, miscellaneous archives
  - Miscellaneous., 002785